

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- Javascript
- Angular / Angular JS
- ReactJS
- NodeJS / Express
- Socket.io
- HTML / CSS / SCSS / LESS / SASS
- MongoDB, PostgreSQL, MySQL
- REST
- Python / Pytorch for ML
- Php

DEVELOPMENT TOOLS

- Git
- Jira
- Azure
- SonarCloud
- Jenkins

PERSONAL SKILLS

- Reliable and professional
- Organised
- Punctual
- Team player
- Fast learner
- Motivated
- Curious

LANGUAGES

- English
- Romanian

CONTACT

Phone: +40 730 799 252 Email: silviualexd@gmail.com

GitHub: https://github.com/SilviuDinu

SILVIU-ALEXANDRU DINU

ABOUT

I am a curious and sociable person, able to work in a team or independently. I have nearly 2 years of working experience with the Web Development technologies.

I always tend to exceed my expectations, and I am always passionate about any project I am working on. I like learning new things and following best practices.

WORK EXPERIENCE

MIDDLE FRONTEND DEVELOPER

EPAM SYSTEMS, Bucharest I Oct. 2021 - Present Day

- Delivering top tier services for our clients.
- Working with tools like: AngularJS, Angular, NodeJS, Jira

CONSULTANT - MIDDLE FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Deloitte Digital, Bucharest I Feb. 2020 - Oct. 2021

- Actively engaged with our clients to ensure top-of-the-line services & consultancy through my work.
- Working with tools like: AngularJS, Angular, React, SCSS, Jira

JUNIOR PROGRAMMER - TECHNICAL SUPPORT ENGINEER

Themelsle, Bucharest | Jul. 2018 - Feb. 2020

- Aiding customers to build reliable WordPress websites
- Solving/reporting bugs and debugging (PHP, CSS, JavaScript, MySQL)

EDUCATION

BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN SYSTEMS ENGINEERING

Faculty of Automatic Control and Computer Science, University POLITEHNICA of Bucharest \mid 2016 - 2020

PROGRESSING TOWARDS A MASTER'S DEGREE IN ADVANCED SIGNAL PROCESSING

Faculty of Automatic Control and Computer Science, University POLITEHNICA of Bucharest | 2020 - Present

PROJECTS / COURSES

REACT WEATHER APP

A weather app built with React and Express which enables the user to search the weather in certain cities around the world. The app automatically detects your location and displays the weather information that is most relevant to you.

Used tools: React Hooks, React router, Express, REST APIs, Typescript, MongoDB https://forecast-report.com/

WEB SOCKETS CHAT

A web chat application built with React on the FE and socket.io running on the BE. Users can connect to the chat room and exchange messages with each other.

Used tools: React Hooks, Node.JS, Websockets, Socket.io, Typescript https://github.com/SilviuDinu/web-sockets-chat

URL SHORTENER

A web app created with Vue.JS and Express that enables the users to create shortURLs.

Used tools: Vue.JS, Express, MongoDB https://slv.lol/